<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Season 2 on Nyxipedia</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/</link><description>Recent content in Season 2 on Nyxipedia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S02E01</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e01/</guid><description>S02E01 # Lullaby Lounge: Season 2 Premiere
Aired: 2020-06-23 Posted: 2020-08-09
This episode was the first of season 2, and the change-over to Tuesday nights. Kate had taken a break for about 2 months to let her voice recover from some serious strain. This episode was also the first with &amp;ldquo;The Part Where I Talk&amp;rdquo; including a proto-version of the jingle.
I wanna tell you a story, about why I became the type of musician that I am today.</description></item><item><title>S02E02</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e02/</guid><description>S02E02 # Lullaby Lounge: Bardic Inspiration
Aired: 2020-06-30 Posted: 2020-08-09
This episode included the show&amp;rsquo;s first dance break, set to Take a Knee. Quoted below is a particularly interesting story about Kate&amp;rsquo;s background in the renaissance faire that was told during this episode.
I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell my story tonight of when I used to work at the Pennsylvania Renaissance Faire. Um. For those of you who didn&amp;rsquo;t know, or couldn&amp;rsquo;t guess, I worked at a renaissance faire from ages fourteen to seventeen.</description></item><item><title>S02E03</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e03/</guid><description>S02E03 # Lullaby Lounge: Songs To Cry To
Aired: 2020-07-07 Posted: 2020-08-09
Setlist # Purgatory - Kate Nyx Hurt - Johnny Cash (originally Nine Inch Nails) Part of Your World - Jodi Benson (from The Little Mermaid) You Don&amp;rsquo;t See Me - Kay Hanley (from Josie and the Pussycats) Crying Wolf - Kate Nyx Pretty Girl - Kate Nyx Iris - Goo Goo Dolls</description></item><item><title>S02E04</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e04/</guid><description>S02E04 # Lullaby Lounge: ONE YEAR ANNIVERSARY
Aired: 2020-07-14 Posted: 2020-08-09
Fifty-two weeks in a row of the Lullaby Lounge were marked as of this episode, and it also was a Dicebreak! Kate showed a clip of the very first Lullaby Lounge episode just before the midroll, which was a nice surprise!
Kate Nyx S02E04
Setlist # A Cloak of Elvenkind - Marcy Playground What You Feel - Buffy The Vampire Slayer: Once More, With Feeling RE: Your Brains - Jonathan Coulton Kiss From a Rose - Seal Ren Faire Romance - Kate Nyx The Adventure Begins - Critical Role Videogames &amp;amp; Porn - Kate Nyx Still Alive - Kate Nyx</description></item><item><title>S02E05</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e05/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e05/</guid><description>S02E05 # Lullaby Lounge: Songs To Kill A Man To
Aired: 2020-07-21 Posted: 2020-08-08
Is that a huge cup or am I tiny? I am a medium-sized lady. This is a huge cup. I would say&amp;hellip; I have a very large head. Like&amp;hellip; I have an extra large head. Um. For those of you that do not know, I have the same size head as, like, like a 300 pound adult man.</description></item><item><title>S02E06</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e06/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e06/</guid><description>S02E06 # Lullaby Lounge: Angry Girl Music of the Indie/Rock Persuasion
Aired: 2020-07-28 Posted: 2020-08-09
So. This week&amp;rsquo;s part where I talk is a little bit of a story, not so much a&amp;ndash; well, there&amp;rsquo;s a little bit of a message to it. We&amp;rsquo;ll see where it goes. Um. So, back in the before times, um, back right around, right before I started, before I released my third record, idiot child.</description></item><item><title>S02E07</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e07/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-2/s02e07/</guid><description>S02E07 # Lullaby Lounge: Season Twosday Finale
Aired: 2020-08-04 Posted: 2020-08-09
This episode truly celebrated season twosday in style. Tip goal was met and exceeded incredibly early, a heartfelt The Part Where I Talk (quoted below) was had, and there was even a dancebreak featuring Ophidian! It also featured the premiere of Bean Gotta Scream, and an early rendition of a Lullaby Lounge theme.
I have a lot of feelings right now.</description></item></channel></rss>