<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Season 1 on Nyxipedia</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/</link><description>Recent content in Season 1 on Nyxipedia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S01E19289</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19289/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19289/</guid><description>S01E19289 # The Lovefool Visits The Lullaby Lounge
Aired: 2019-10-16
Setlist # Just Another of My Glitches - Kate Nyx little girl, BIG LIAR - Kate Nyx A Boy in Black - Kate Nyx Why Don&amp;rsquo;t You Do Right - Peggy Lee/Jessica Rabbit Kiss From a Rose - Seal Calm Down - Kate Nyx Beautiful Mistake - Kate Nyx Howl - Florence and the Machine Partner in Crime - Kate Nyx The Middle - Jimmy Eat World You Don&amp;rsquo;t Own Me - Lesley Gore</description></item><item><title>S01E19296</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19296/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19296/</guid><description>S01E19296 # Occult Outlaw - Southern Gothic Folk
Aired: 2019-10-16
Setlist # Crying Wolf - Kate Nyx Let Me In - Code Orange Spring Cleaning - Kate Nyx Crazy - Patsy Cline Hurt - Johnny Cash (yes, originally Nine Inch Nails, but this is clearly Johnny Cash&amp;rsquo;s cover being covered) Under Covers - Kate Nyx Black Sky Lullaby - Kate Nyx Bootstraps - Kate Nyx Road to Hell - Kate Nyx Blood &amp;amp; Bone - Kate Nyx So Pretty When You&amp;rsquo;re Mean - Kate Nyx</description></item><item><title>S01E19310</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19310/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19310/</guid><description>S01E19310 # Bardic Inspiration
Aired: 2019-11-06
Setlist # Holding Out for a Hero - Bonnie Tyler Ballad of the Bard - Kate Nyx I&amp;rsquo;m Gonna Be (500 Miles) - The Proclaimers Ren Faire Romance - Kate Nyx Strong in the Real Way - Steven Universe Don&amp;rsquo;t Send Pictures of Your Dick (?) - Kate Nyx Pretty Girl - Kate Nyx Trigger Warning - Kate Nyx Kiss From a Rose - Kate Nyx</description></item><item><title>S01E19317</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19317/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19317/</guid><description>S01E19317 # Lullaby Lounge at Turkey Point - Cry Baby theme
Aired: 2019-11-13
Setlist # Annabelle - Kate Nyx Fly Me To The Moon - Bart Howard (Frank Sinatra?) Welcome to Facebook - Kate Nyx A Teenage Prayer - Rachel Sweet Clap If You Believe - Kate Nyx Please Share - Kate Nyx Changeling - Kate Nyx Sell Out - Kate Nyx Patreon Song - Kate Nyx Please, Mr.</description></item><item><title>S01E19324</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19324/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19324/</guid><description>S01E19324 # Lullaby Lounge DELUXE
Aired: 2019-11-20
In this episode we found out about Kate&amp;rsquo;s 100 year old ukulele Marlena. It&amp;rsquo;s also a storytelling episode! A tale of woe circling a circus-running spider and a songbird in love with him. But, perhaps, one of hope and strength as well!
Setlist # Nature Boy - David Bowie and Massive Attack As the World Falls Down - David Bowie Toxic Love - Tim Curry (from FernGully: The Last Rainforest) Within You - David Bowie Patreon Song - Kate Nyx Facebook Song - Kate Nyx Please Share - Kate Nyx Take a Knee - Kate Nyx (with a variant chorus at the end!</description></item><item><title>S01E20008</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20008/</guid><description>S01E20008 # Lullaby Lounge 80s Week
Aired: 2020-01-08
80s week!
Setlist # Holding Out for a Hero - Bonnie Tyler Friday I&amp;rsquo;m in Love - The Cure Heartbreaker - Pat Benatar Part of Your World - Jodi Benson (from The Little Mermaid) Punk Rock Girl - The Dead Milkmen (bonus mouth sounds solo!) Please Share - Kate Nyx Take on Me - a-ha Patreon Song - Kate Nyx Tainted Love - Soft Cell Never Gonna Give You Up - Rick Astley I Hate Myself for Loving You - Joan Jett and the Blackhearts Girls Just Wanna Have Fun - Cyndi Lauper Your Turn to Roll (Critical Role Theme) - Laura Bailey, Ashley Johnson and Sam Riegel (a cappella) Jeannie - Hugo Montenegro (from I Dream of Jeannie)</description></item><item><title>S01E20015</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20015/</guid><description>S01E20015 # Lullaby Lounge VINTAGE KATE edition
Aired: 2020-01-08
This episode had an unfortunate audio sync problem where the audio is delayed by a few seconds from the video.
Setlist # It&amp;rsquo;ll Be Okay - Remnants of Alice/Kate Nyx and Ashley Hart Licorice Tree - Kate Nyx Three Small Words - Josie and the Pussycats (Kay Hanley) Be My Valentine - Kate Nyx</description></item></channel></rss>