<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Season 1 on Nyxipedia</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/</link><description>Recent content in Season 1 on Nyxipedia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S01E19289</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19289/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19289/</guid><description>S01E19289 # The Lovefool Visits The Lullaby Lounge
Aired: 2019-10-16
Setlist # Just Another of My Glitches - Kate Nyx little girl, BIG LIAR - Kate Nyx A Boy in Black - Kate Nyx Why Don&amp;rsquo;t You Do Right - Peggy Lee/Jessica Rabbit Kiss From a Rose - Seal Calm Down - Kate Nyx Beautiful Mistake - Kate Nyx Howl - Florence and the Machine Partner in Crime - Kate Nyx The Middle - Jimmy Eat World You Don&amp;rsquo;t Own Me - Lesley Gore</description></item><item><title>S01E19296</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19296/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19296/</guid><description>S01E19296 # Occult Outlaw - Southern Gothic Folk
Aired: 2019-10-16
Setlist # Crying Wolf - Kate Nyx Let Me In - Code Orange Spring Cleaning - Kate Nyx Crazy - Patsy Cline Hurt - Johnny Cash (yes, originally Nine Inch Nails, but this is clearly Johnny Cash&amp;rsquo;s cover being covered) Under Covers - Kate Nyx Black Sky Lullaby - Kate Nyx Bootstraps - Kate Nyx Road to Hell - Kate Nyx Blood &amp;amp; Bone - Kate Nyx So Pretty When You&amp;rsquo;re Mean - Kate Nyx</description></item><item><title>S01E19310</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19310/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19310/</guid><description>S01E19310 # Bardic Inspiration
Aired: 2019-11-06
Setlist # Holding Out for a Hero - Bonnie Tyler Ballad of the Bard - Kate Nyx I&amp;rsquo;m Gonna Be (500 Miles) - The Proclaimers Ren Faire Romance - Kate Nyx Strong in the Real Way - Steven Universe Don&amp;rsquo;t Send Pictures of Your Dick (?) - Kate Nyx Pretty Girl - Kate Nyx Trigger Warning - Kate Nyx Kiss From a Rose - Seal</description></item><item><title>S01E19317</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19317/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19317/</guid><description>S01E19317 # Lullaby Lounge at Turkey Point - Cry Baby theme
Aired: 2019-11-13
Setlist # Annabelle - Kate Nyx Fly Me To The Moon - Bart Howard (Frank Sinatra?) Welcome to Facebook - Kate Nyx A Teenage Prayer - Rachel Sweet Clap If You Believe - Kate Nyx Please Share - Kate Nyx Changeling - Kate Nyx Sell Out - Kate Nyx Patreon Song - Kate Nyx Please, Mr.</description></item><item><title>S01E19324</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19324/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e19324/</guid><description>S01E19324 # Lullaby Lounge DELUXE
Aired: 2019-11-20
In this episode we found out about Kate&amp;rsquo;s 100 year old ukulele Marlene. It&amp;rsquo;s also a storytelling episode! A tale of woe circling a circus-running spider and a songbird in love with him. But, perhaps, one of hope and strength as well!
Setlist # Nature Boy - David Bowie and Massive Attack As the World Falls Down - David Bowie Toxic Love - Tim Curry (from FernGully: The Last Rainforest) Within You - David Bowie Patreon Song - Kate Nyx Facebook Song - Kate Nyx Please Share - Kate Nyx Take a Knee - Kate Nyx (with a variant chorus at the end!</description></item><item><title>S01E20008</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20008/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20008/</guid><description>S01E20008 # Lullaby Lounge 80s Week
Aired: 2020-01-08
80s week!
Setlist # Holding Out for a Hero - Bonnie Tyler Friday I&amp;rsquo;m in Love - The Cure Heartbreaker - Pat Benatar Part of Your World - Jodi Benson (from The Little Mermaid) Punk Rock Girl - The Dead Milkmen (bonus mouth sounds solo!) Please Share - Kate Nyx Take on Me - a-ha Patreon Song - Kate Nyx Tainted Love - Soft Cell Never Gonna Give You Up - Rick Astley I Hate Myself for Loving You - Joan Jett and the Blackhearts Girls Just Wanna Have Fun - Cyndi Lauper Your Turn to Roll (Critical Role Theme) - Laura Bailey, Ashley Johnson and Sam Riegel (a cappella) Jeannie - Hugo Montenegro (from I Dream of Jeannie)</description></item><item><title>S01E20015</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20015/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20015/</guid><description>S01E20015 # Lullaby Lounge VINTAGE KATE edition
Aired: 2020-01-15
This episode had an unfortunate audio sync problem where the audio is delayed by a few seconds from the video. It&amp;rsquo;s a semi-chronological journey through Kate&amp;rsquo;s work showing her evolution over time. She also mentions an album currently unavailable on her Bandcamp, To My Sisters&amp;hellip; The title track to that album is available on The Dollhouse Collection. She mentioned an EP called Bleed for Me which is unreleased.</description></item><item><title>S01E20029</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20029/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20029/</guid><description>S01E20029 # Lullaby Lounge Pride (&amp;ldquo;Make it Gay live stream&amp;rdquo;)
Aired: 2020-01-29
This episode opens with a few pre-recorded portions. The Best You&amp;rsquo;ve Ever Had, followed by Mein Herr (a cover originally by Liza Minnelli), then a recording of Kate&amp;rsquo;s first gig in 2006 where she played Beautiful Dead. Then a brief tour of Kate&amp;rsquo;s workspace for Closet Champion. Then Don&amp;rsquo;t Block the Box. Then behind the scenes clips from Kate&amp;rsquo;s Fell In Love With a Girl video.</description></item><item><title>S01E20036</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20036/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20036/</guid><description>S01E20036 # Lullaby Lounge (Classics)
Aired: 2020-03-04
This episode opens with a Q&amp;amp;A about Kate&amp;rsquo;s work on wrestling gear.
Setlist # Diagnonsense - Kate Nyx little girl, BIG LIAR - Kate Nyx The Magic - Kate Nyx Clint Eastwood - Gorillaz Blood and Bone - Kate Nyx Annabelle - Kate Nyx Heroine - Kate Nyx &amp;hellip;Baby One More Time - Britney Spears</description></item><item><title>S01E20043</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20043/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20043/</guid><description>S01E20043 # Lullaby Lounge (Valentine&amp;rsquo;s day week stream)
Aired: 2020-02-12
This episode included Kate&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;babe with bodyhair&amp;rdquo; video, as well as The Power of Personal Glamour. Kate attempted to play Trogdor during this stream, but couldn&amp;rsquo;t get it on the fly. Maybe some other time!
Setlist # Don&amp;rsquo;t Block the Box - Kate Nyx Don&amp;rsquo;t Send Pictures of Your Dick - Kate Nyx You Oughta Know - Alanis Morissette Dead Men Can&amp;rsquo;t Catcall - Kate Nyx Spring Cleaning - Kate Nyx What Would Peggy Carter Do?</description></item><item><title>S01E20051</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20051/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20051/</guid><description>S01E20051 # Lullaby Lounge (Choose Your Own Adventure Edition)
Aired: 2020-02-20
This episode is abnormally short due to technical difficulties. Presumably it kept going, but the YouTube version ends during the midroll. This show was played significantly earlier in the day than normal and on a Thursday because Kate had a scheduling conflict at normal showtime. The way the setlist was set up is that Kate picked a bunch of songs in advance and randomized the order via die rolling during the show.</description></item><item><title>S01E20055</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20055/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20055/</guid><description>S01E20055 # Lullaby Lounge (unprepared edition)
Aired: 2020-02-24
This show was the week of PAX, and Kate was slammed with getting ready for it. At the start, Kate talked a bit about her guitar Melissa, a limited-edition Ovation slimline acoustic. In the middle, famed wrestler Ophidian the Cobra busted onto the set and stopped the show to put Kate through a training montage featuring Smacktalk Showdown, a game she&amp;rsquo;d be playing on stage at PAX a few days after this show.</description></item><item><title>S01E20064</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20064/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20064/</guid><description>S01E20064 # Lullaby Lounge low key edition
Aired: 2020-03-04
This episode opens with a few pre-recorded portions. Mein Herr (a cover originally by Liza Minnelli), then a recording of Kate&amp;rsquo;s first gig in 2006 where she played Beautiful Dead. Then a brief tour of Kate&amp;rsquo;s workspace for Closet Champion. Then Don&amp;rsquo;t Block the Box. Then behind the scenes clips from Kate&amp;rsquo;s Fell In Love With a Girl video.</description></item><item><title>S01E20078</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20078/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20078/</guid><description>S01E20078 # Lullaby Lounge with special guest Ophidian the Cobra
Aired: 2020-03-18
As titled, Ophidian hung out for this episode.
Setlist # Clint Eastwood - Gorillaz (feat. Ophidian) Death to Amasis - Ophidian the Cobra Blood and Bone - Kate Nyx (feat. Ophidian) Sell out! - Kate Nyx Numb - Linkin Park (feat. Ophidian) In The End - Linkin Park (feat. Ophidian) Faith - George Michael (feat.</description></item><item><title>S01E20085</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20085/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20085/</guid><description>S01E20085 # Lullaby Lounge: Power Up Edition
Aired: 2020-03-25
This episode&amp;rsquo;s theme was about powering up and using music to do so. One notable moment was when Kate played Pretty Girl, she did so on guitar, and a significant portion of the song was more upbeat and intense.
I&amp;rsquo;m very glamourous, in that I sweat constantly and I smell terrible.
Kate Nyx Setlist # Black Sky Lullaby - Kate Nyx Warrior of Love - Kate Nyx The Magic - Kate Nyx Pretty Girl - Kate Nyx Kiss From a Rose - Seal What Would Peggy Carter Do?</description></item><item><title>S01E20092</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20092/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20092/</guid><description>S01E20092 # LULLABY LOUNGE: ROCK EDITION
Aired: 2020-04-01
This episode is exactly what the title says, featuring rock focused songs. It also has a whole lot of important quotes, including an explanation of Kate referring to her community as LODESTARs.
Alright. Who is ready TO ROCK? I know that I started this in a little bit of a flustered state. I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to taking out that pent up energy and anger at myself and putting it into something worthwhile, using music.</description></item><item><title>S01E20099</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20099/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20099/</guid><description>S01E20099 # Lullaby Lounge: Soothing Springtime
Aired: 2020-04-08
The previous week&amp;rsquo;s show was really intense, so Kate made this one a lot more low key and chill. Lots of slower, quieter songs, after nearly blowing out her voice the previous week.
One of the things that, um, I get kind of&amp;hellip; When the trolls do come for me, on the rare occasion, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen that often.</description></item><item><title>S01E20106</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20106/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20106/</guid><description>S01E20106 # Lullaby Lounge: DICEBREAK!
Aired: 2020-04-15
The tagline for this episode was &amp;ldquo;Chosen by Fate, Performed by Kate.&amp;rdquo; A ten-sided die was rolled to decide what songs to play, live on the show.
Setlist # Ballad of the Bard - Kate Nyx What You Feel - Buffy The Vampire Slayer: Once More, With Feeling Kiss From a Rose - Seal The Magic - Kate Nyx Spooky - Dusty Springfield Black Sky Lullaby - Kate Nyx changeling - Kate Nyx Diagnonsense - Kate Nyx Better Half - Kate Nyx Crying Wolf - Kate Nyx</description></item><item><title>S01E20113</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20113/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-1/s01e20113/</guid><description>S01E20113 # Lullaby Lounge: Songs Everyone Hates But You
Aired: 2020-04-22
Listen. I&amp;rsquo;m overwhelming you with information that doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter to you, which is sort of my M.O. You know, listen, I pitch a lot of elevators, Fred. I pitch a lot of elevators. Listen, I&amp;rsquo;m throwin&amp;rsquo; elevators left and right in this bitch. How do you think I take you from Streamland to Dreamland if I&amp;rsquo;m not throwin&amp;rsquo; some elevators?</description></item></channel></rss>