<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TRASH GOBLIN SMASH HITS Vol. 2 on Nyxipedia</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/</link><description>Recent content in TRASH GOBLIN SMASH HITS Vol. 2 on Nyxipedia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bet It On The Boostraps</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/bet-it-on-the-bootstraps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/bet-it-on-the-bootstraps/</guid><description> Bet It On The Boostraps # Lyrics # welcome to the ratrace racetrack honeywhere you gonna put that put that moneyyou look like you could use some helpmaybe you should learn to help yourselfyou can bet it all on duloxetineon yoga, cyclobenzaprinebut i say bet it on the bootstrapsbet it on the bootstrapsyou can bet it all on duloxetineon yoga, cyclobenzaprinebut i say bet in on the bootstrapsbad luck never looked so goodprettiest pauper in the neighborhoodman down, stand down, please, god, take the painturns out god doesn’t take medicaidyou can bet it all on duloxetineon yoga, cyclobenzaprinebut i say bet it on the bootstrapsbet it on the bootstrapsyou can bet it all on DBTon diet, prayer, and therapybut i say bet in on the bootstrapshave faith in yourself[bet it, bet it, bet it on the bootstraps]and trust no one else[bet it, bet it, bet it on the bootstraps]have faith in yourself[bet it, bet it, bet it on the bootstraps]and trust no oneand trust no one elsebet it on the bootstrapsbet it on the bootstrapsyou can bet it all on DBTon diet, prayer, and therapybut i say bet it on the bootstrapsbet it on the bootstrapsbet it on the bootstrapsbet it on the bootstraps</description></item><item><title>changeling</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/changeling/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/changeling/</guid><description> changeling # Lyrics # take me back under the moundi am lost and can’t be foundtake me back under the moundi am losti don’t belong herei don’t belong herei’ve felt it for a long timesomething’s going on herei don’t rememberI don’t rememberyou say it was just yesterdaybut it seems like forevertake me back under the moundi am lost and can’t be foundtake me back under the moundi am lostmy flesh betrays meit disobeys mepretending i’m not gossamerhas gutted and fileted mei can’t surrenderi don’t rememberyou say it’s been a couple monthsbut it feels like forevertake me back under the moundi am lost and can’t be foundtake me back under the moundi am losti am lostin ironsidetake me back under the moundi am lost and can’t be foundtake me back under the moundi am lost</description></item><item><title>Clap If You Believe</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/clap-if-you-believe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/clap-if-you-believe/</guid><description>Clap If You Believe # Lyrics # My light is going outIt’s getting darker nowI tried to save you all somehowBut I can’t save myselfI used to be so brightA star among the nightIlluminating, I’m alrightBut now I’ve lost my shineI’ve been drinking poison far too long and deepBarreling desperately towards my eternal sleepI’ve always been there to look before you leapNow I need you to clap if you believeI’ve been afraid to askBut now I’m fading fastAnd so at longest lastI’m reaching for your handIve been drinking poison far too sickly sweetdesperately trying not to give in to diseaseI’ve always been there to think before you speakNow I need you to clap if you believeMy light is going dimThey say power is withinSo maybe there’s no way to winThis game I never wanted to play.</description></item><item><title>Closing Theme</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/closing-theme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/closing-theme/</guid><description>Closing Theme # Lyrics # Please like (like! like!)And subscribe (subscribe)We can't guarantee it's worth it; you won't know if you don't tryAnd before (before)We say goodbye (goodbye)There is one more little thing, to help us out, if you don't mind;To show us you really careGive this video a shareAnd though we are sad to watch you go,We'll see you in the comments down below!(spoken)Moxie: I like singing with you, Kate.</description></item><item><title>Crying Wolf</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/crying-wolf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/crying-wolf/</guid><description> Crying Wolf # Lyrics # woke up crying out in paintaking the lord’s name in vainwent to the doctor, he said “no,i can’t see it, it’s not so,you’re just thinking so damn hardpretty thing, you’re seeing starstake a rest, this will subside”he thinks that I’m telling liesi can see it in his eyesawoooshe is crying wolf, she’s just crying wolfshe might be sick but i’ve seen sickerwhy smoke grass when you’ve got liquorwhy drink gin when whiskey’s sweeterwhy pay paul when you stillill owe peterwhy say red when you mean greywhy say go when you mean staywhy purr when you want to growlwhy wait, sister, do it now,bare your teeth and howlawoooshe is crying wolf, she’s just crying wolfwounded but i do not bleedhow can i heal what i can’t seewounded but they don’t believehow can i heal what i can’t seeawoooshe is crying wolf, she’s just crying wolf</description></item><item><title>Crying Wolf [Backbreaker Mix]</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/crying-wolf-backbreaker-mix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/crying-wolf-backbreaker-mix/</guid><description> Crying Wolf [Backbreaker Mix] # Background # A remix of my original song, Crying Wolf.
Lyrics # woke up crying out in paintaking the lord’s name in vainwent to the doctor, he said “no,i can’t see it, it’s not so,you’re just thinking so damn hardpretty thing, you’re seeing starstake a rest, this will subside”he thinks that I’m telling liesi can see it in his eyesawoooshe is crying wolf, she’s just crying wolfshe might be sick but i’ve seen sickerwhy smoke grass when you’ve got liquorwhy drink gin when whiskey’s sweeterwhy pay paul when you stillill owe peterwhy say red when you mean greywhy say go when you mean staywhy purr when you want to growlwhy wait, sister, do it now,bare your teeth and howlawoooshe is crying wolf, she’s just crying wolfwounded but i do not bleedhow can i heal what i can’t seewounded but they don’t believehow can i heal what i can’t seeawoooshe is crying wolf, she’s just crying wolf</description></item><item><title>heroine [DEMO]</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/heroine-demo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/heroine-demo/</guid><description> heroine [DEMO] # Lyrics # watching as the fire consumes uswaiting, praying for the raini want to help but i feel helplesslike there’s nothing i can changewho am i when i’m not givingwho am i when i receivehow am can i just keep on livingwatching others as they bleedi know that i’m supposed to seea light right there in front of mebut i see only darkness up aheadi know that i’m supposed to findsomeway to keep me peace of mindbut i fear the only peace i’ll find is deathwatching as the clock is tickingwaiting, praying for relief,I can feel my conscience slippingas I fade back in to sleepi know that i’m supposed to fightI know that none of this is rightbut I can barely stand on my two feeti want to be your heroineI want to love my home againbut this burlesques reveals no part for meJust what am i supposed to doWhen lies have gone and murdered truthWhen hearts cannot be heard over the screamsThe ghost of our democracyis not enough to comfort meAnd if I must, I’ll fight to live my dream</description></item><item><title>Hey There</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/hey-there/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/hey-there/</guid><description> Hey There # Lyrics # Hey there, pretty boyYou don't get to make my choiceHey there, pretty boyDon't you tread on meThis has been long time comingAnd you better speak the truthWhen you make a deal with the devilHe is gonna follow youYou can say that we are huntersI guess that makes you the preyYou can run but you can't hide nowThe witches have come out to playHey there, pretty boyYou don't get to take my voiceHey there, pretty boyDon't you tread on meYou protect the wolf among youYou play blind and grant reprieveBut he howls and bites and growlsAnd leaves a trail of bloody sheepYou can say that you're our sisterBut you speak with silver tonguesYou can't tame a wolf or misterAnd you'll pay for what you've doneHey there, pretty girl,Watch your step, this ain’t our worldHey there, pretty girl,Don't you tread on me</description></item><item><title>Money Talks [Demo]</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/money-talks-demo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/money-talks-demo/</guid><description>Money Talks [Demo] # Lyrics # I won't be quietI won't be ignoredI've had it with your lies andWon't wait around for moreYou tell me that you love meYou tell me I'm adoredBut your actions speak much louder than your money can affordI won't be silentI will not lay downI said I won't be quietNow listen to the soundI'm sure you think you know meYour pretty little clownBut I am no one's fool, you hear?</description></item><item><title>Of Lily &amp; Lorelei</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/of-lily-and-lorelei/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/of-lily-and-lorelei/</guid><description>Of Lily &amp;amp; Lorelei # Lyrics # Lily was a good girl, she wore white cotton laceNever did you see her without a smile on her faceShe was marrying an artist with a heart of goldShe loved him for his smile and the stories that he toldLorelei, her sister, wasn't such a pleasant dameShe wore dark sunglasses and laughed at those in painShe saw Lily's fiancee waiting for her by the stairsStripped him in a second, and danced away without a careLorelei, my loveLorelei, my loveI could never love youlike the pain you cause does.</description></item><item><title>Pretty Girl [A Lullaby]</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/pretty-girl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/pretty-girl/</guid><description>Pretty Girl [A Lullaby] # Background # It is time for a song that I have written. Not for a lost love, or a woman I was in love with, but for another queer woman who I am friends with&amp;hellip; Trying to be friends with again. And I wrote this song for her daughter. And I wrote it, I think around her daughter&amp;rsquo;s first birthday. And, um, we fell out of contact due to some actions on her part.</description></item><item><title>Trigger Warning</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/trigger-warning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/trigger-warning/</guid><description>Trigger Warning # Lyrics # Times up, butter cup, I just had a premonitionSomeday soon I’ll confiscate your ammunitionAs it turns out, boys like you tend to go crazyI think that that kinda weapon’s safer with a pretty ladyThat’s nice, mister man, sure, I think you’re very smartBut that kind of privilege isn’t for the faint of heartWhat if your wife leaves you for a bigger better Tom or DickAnd you go shoot up a school because you can’t handle your shit?</description></item><item><title>Trying [2017 Demo]</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/trying/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/trash-goblin-smash-hits-vol-2/trying/</guid><description>Trying [2017 Demo] # Background # This was made in fall of 2017, at the height of my chronic illness thus far.
Lyrics # (spoken)That's rightAnother white girl with Garageband(sung)I wanna share with you the truth of truths[[unintelligible]], and so what have I got to lose?Vulnerable is valiant with the right coat of paintSo who says that I have to learn restraintI wanna share with you my heart of heartsJust stitch me up so I can't come apartSo crucify me for the sake of artIt's what I need so I can startMy path to progress, it isn't a straight lineAnd if you say "</description></item></channel></rss>