<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Season 6 - Lullaby Lounge Novelty Hour on Nyxipedia</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/</link><description>Recent content in Season 6 - Lullaby Lounge Novelty Hour on Nyxipedia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>S06E01</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06e01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06e01/</guid><description>S06E01 # The season premiere of the Lullaby Lounge Novelty Hour!
Aired: 2021-08-17
Segments # Paranormal Pawn Commercial 1 Motivation with Moxie 1 Trash Goblin Institute For Goblin Who Can&amp;rsquo;t Trash Good 1 Magic Bartender 1 So You Think You Can Frog Dex Wrex 1 (pigeon with a gun) Novelty After Hours 1 The Part Where I Talk 1 Setlist # Nature Boy - David Bowie and Massive Attack All Star - Smash Mouth Luv Mice Elf - Kate Nyx Of Lily and Lorelei - Kate Nyx Santeria - Sublime Centerfold - The J.</description></item><item><title>S06E02</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06e02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06e02/</guid><description>S06E02 # The second episode of the Lullaby Lounge Novelty Hour! This week&amp;rsquo;s theme was &amp;ldquo;Back 2 School [90s Edition]&amp;rdquo;
Aired: 2021-08-24
Segments # Paranormal Pawn Commercial 2 Motivation with Moxie 2 The Price is Frog Dex Wrex 2 Novelty After Hours 2 The Part Where I Talk 2 The &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m seventeen, y&amp;rsquo;all!&amp;rdquo; Story Setlist # (You Drive Me) Crazy - Britney Spears Arise Fair Sun - Kate Nyx Iris - Goo Goo Dolls Can&amp;rsquo;t Take My Eyes Off of You - Frankie Valli Modern Dating - Kate Nyx Don&amp;rsquo;t Stop Me Now - Queen (a cappella) Wonderwall - Oasis Kiss Me - Sixpence None The Richer &amp;hellip;Baby One More Time - Britney Spears</description></item><item><title>S06E03</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06e03/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06e03/</guid><description>S06E03 # The third episode of the Lullaby Lounge Novelty Hour! This week&amp;rsquo;s theme was &amp;ldquo;Bardic Inspiration.&amp;rdquo; This episode also guest starred Lindsey Noel! Additionally, had one long, overarching, scripted segment, because it was a cohesive story written in conjunction with producer Grace Briarwood!
Aired: 2021-08-31
Segments # Magic Trick 1 A tale about Princess Melia of the Green Kingdom, Meppior. Paranormal Pawn Grand Opening Magic Trick 2 Novelty After Hours 3 The Part Where I Talk 3 Magic Trick 3 Would You Rather An Unexpected Visit From Margot Starlux, and the Pizza Wolf story (awooooo) Kate Performing a Makeup Removal Routine While Accompanying Herself on Kazoo feat.</description></item><item><title>S06E04</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06e04/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06e04/</guid><description>S06E04 # THE LULLABY LOUNGE NOVELTY HOUR Goes To The Circus
During this week&amp;rsquo;s show, there were some major technical difficulties. The Network&amp;rsquo;s signal was severely disrupted for unknown reasons. The GOOCroo was on it, but it was a serious struggle. At one point, Kate even ended upside-down!
Aired: 2021-08-17
Segments # Fell In Love With a Girl Music Video Speaking a bit about Kate&amp;rsquo;s history of burlesque performing Learning Got-Got With Margot Starlux Spring Cleaning Music Video Trash Goblin Institute For Goblin Who Can&amp;rsquo;t Trash Good 2 1-800-REPLY-GUY The Part Where I Talk 4 Setlist # Circus - Britney Spears Don&amp;rsquo;t Block the Box - Kate Nyx Trigger Warning - Kate Nyx So Pretty When You&amp;rsquo;re Mean - Kate Nyx Baby Got Back [Alternate Lyrics] - Kate Nyx feat Ophidian Ugly Sick &amp;amp; Strange - Kate Nyx I Don&amp;rsquo;t Want to Be an Artist - Kate Nyx</description></item><item><title>S06S01</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06s01/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/lullaby-lounge/seasons/season-6/s06s01/</guid><description>S06S01 # A special episode called the Rewind Revue, where Kate hung out with the chat and played selected clips from the current season.
Aired: 2021-09-07</description></item></channel></rss>