<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unreleased Songs on Nyxipedia</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/</link><description>Recent content in Unreleased Songs on Nyxipedia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2 Poor 2 Flex</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/2-poor-2-flex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/2-poor-2-flex/</guid><description>2 Poor 2 Flex # Background # So, this goofy phrase popped into my head this morning; 2 Poor 2 Flex, numeric linguistic situation included. I knew that it deserved an equally goofy rap to match&amp;hellip;
So I busted this out of my brain today. The arrangement isn&amp;rsquo;t finished; it needs more than just bass and drums as far as instrumentation goes, and the mix is rough, but the ideas are there.</description></item><item><title>A Faerie Ballad</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/a-faerie-ballad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/a-faerie-ballad/</guid><description>A Faerie Ballad # Background # As many of you know, last year, one of our external hard drives crashed, losing us over a decade of videos, music, and various other projects.
Fortunately, I was able to locate some of my music and lyrics on my old laptop, which has stayed on long enough for me to transfer them over to another hard drive.
This song is still kind of unnamed; the title of the document for the lyrics is &amp;ldquo;Compare thee&amp;rdquo;, the file is called &amp;ldquo;a faerie ballad&amp;rdquo; and I think I released it on MySpace at some point under the title &amp;ldquo;siren song&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>All This to Say</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/all-this-to-say/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/all-this-to-say/</guid><description>All This to Say # Background # Kate had this stuck in her head the day before Thanksgiving 2021, and demoed it live on Instagram that day. Various keys were tried, but she hadn&amp;rsquo;t settled on one yet at the time of this writing. According to her, it&amp;rsquo;s going back to her pop-punk roots and she was inspired to write it after seeing that Avril Lavigne had released new music.</description></item><item><title>Arithmetic</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/arithmetic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/arithmetic/</guid><description>Arithmetic # Background # At one point, Kate was working on a project to write or record a new song every day in the month of August. This is one that came out of that project. This song has never had a dedicated recording, other than the YouTube video.
Lyrics # Let's do the mathFirst subtractThe three years that passed in tearsThat I'll never get backSo relaxI'm not a scholarBut I'm willing to bet at least a couple dollarsThat I'm better off without the stressCaused by that whole fuckin' messBut I still can't forget the shitThat I let him get away withBut backTo the pointYou plus me equalsGod who knowsLet's see how the equation goesOh, you plus me equalsGod who knowsLet's see how the equation goesSo four yearsMinus the tearsIs a year or soAnd I still didn't let goI hold onTo my hopeAnd here we are, four months or soInto something wonderfulWell at least it is so farSubtract the months we've spent apartWaiting to seeI wouldn't runSo what are we at?</description></item><item><title>Be My Valentine</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/be-my-valentine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/be-my-valentine/</guid><description>Be My Valentine # Background # This is a song Kate wrote at about 14 years old, and memorable and important because she played it for her first gig at a bar at 16 years old.
Lyrics # Got you candyI bought you flowersStood outside your windowFor three hoursHolding up a stereo like the guy in the movie didWrote you poemsEight love lettersYou don't like meAny betterDo you think I'm serious, or do you think I'm just a kid?</description></item><item><title>Better</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/better/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/better/</guid><description>Better # Background # I’m leaking music out of my bones right now. I think it might be because I went off my Cymbalta; it was supposed to be helping my nerve pain but it just made me suicidal. I’ve rejected my fair share of SSRIs and I don’t know why I thought this would be different. Now, it’s “just” Flexeril, prescription strength aspirin, 2 hour epsom salt baths, crystals, EFT tapping (I’ve gone full hippie), BCAAs, strength training, and my dry herb vape.</description></item><item><title>Better Half</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/better-half/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/better-half/</guid><description>Better Half # Background # I wrote this song back in the summer of 2012, when the cobra and I first started dating. I had gone on a couple auditions for community theaters , and hadn&amp;rsquo;t made it past callbacks for any of them. I decided, in that moment, to write a musical. Both this song and Diagnonsense were from the musical I attempted to write&amp;hellip;about my mental health, call &amp;ldquo;Borderline.</description></item><item><title>Calm Down (We Thrive)</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/calm-down-we-thrive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/calm-down-we-thrive/</guid><description>Calm Down (We Thrive) # Background # During S06E06, Kate performed this alternate version of Calm Down.
Lyrics # Corporate Sponsor knows where you sleepThey monitor all of your dreamsThey know when you cry and you screamTheir observance keeps us all clean, indeedSystems engage, protocol savedThe Network providesUnder control, we are all wholeThank you for our livesWe thriveIt’s impressive all that they knowThey can see you watching the showThey know when you’re sad and aloneTo protect our family and homes, we growSystems engage, protocol savedThe Network providesUnder control, we are all wholeThank you for our livesWe thrive</description></item><item><title>Clan Bloodhammer Battle Song</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/clan-bloodhammer-battle-song/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/clan-bloodhammer-battle-song/</guid><description>Clan Bloodhammer Battle Song # Background # Months ago, I was commissioned for a battle song meant to represent a clan of dwarves called Clan Bloodhammer, meant to be recorded in a folk/fantasy metal style.
It took me forever to cobble all the ideas I had together into one cohesive bunch, but here they are!
Kate Nyx Patreon Lyrics # For flame and forgeFor blood and hammer(repeated throughout song)</description></item><item><title>Coming to a Screen Near You</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/coming-to-a-screen-near-you/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/coming-to-a-screen-near-you/</guid><description>Coming to a Screen Near You # Background # I was complaining on Twitter about not being able to put my gigs up on Spotify because they&amp;rsquo;re all livestreams, but then Shark suggested I write a song about it! I recorded it on Twitch yesterday; it was the first time I ever recorded like that on a livestream and it was so much more difficult than recording by myself.</description></item><item><title>Corporate Sponsor Girl</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/corporate-sponsor-girl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/corporate-sponsor-girl/</guid><description>Corporate Sponsor Girl # Background # During S06E06, Kate performed this alternate version of Supernova Girl.
Lyrics # Glowing with synergyOptimizing energyLiving in an automatic worldYou have your spot in lineThat status suits you fineWould you be my corporate sponsored girl?Interoffice romance must be disclosed or we’re firedBut for you I’d go to HR to sign the forms requiredZoom zoom zoom, make my sales go boom boomMy corporate sponsored girlDreaming of your pretty faceReminds me how you know your placeIn our perfect capitalist worldIf it weren’t for Corpy SponsWe all would be dead and goneWould you be my corporate sponsored girl</description></item><item><title>Crazy Sad &amp; Young</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/crazy-sad-young/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/crazy-sad-young/</guid><description>Crazy Sad &amp;amp; Young # Background # I wrote this in 2013 about dealing with the remnants of a three year abusive relationship a year after leaving it. I&amp;rsquo;ve been considering making a video about what it&amp;rsquo;s been like to fight through the terrible fog connected to that situation and the things I believe about myself because of it. Maybe one day.
Until then, here&amp;rsquo;s a demo that pretty much word for word describes the fight I still have with myself weekly.</description></item><item><title>Death to Amasis</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/death-to-amasis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/death-to-amasis/</guid><description>Death to Amasis # Background # This is a song Ophidian released on his own bandcamp but wrote it with Kate while she was still under the name Hayley Jane. It was performed live on S01E20055. Kate wrote most of the lyrics and rapped it for Ophidian so he could learn it. She said at the time it was made, he was severely lacking in rhythm, but has improved quite a bit since.</description></item><item><title>Don't Block the Box</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/dont-block-the-box/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/dont-block-the-box/</guid><description>Don&amp;#39;t Block the Box # Background # Lyrics # Just mindin' my own business, not trying to catch your eyeYou decided to come talk to me about what's on your mindI'm a pretty open person, yeah, that'd normally be fineYou went on some shameful spiel about how I should live my lifeDon't block the boxDon't block the boxReally, who are you to say who I can and cannot lay?</description></item><item><title>Endless Gold and Ample Green</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/endless-gold-and-ample-green/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/endless-gold-and-ample-green/</guid><description>Endless Gold and Ample Green # Background # I&amp;rsquo;m (tentatively, sort of) working on a concept album; the working title is Seven Spells. I&amp;rsquo;m still in the beginning fooling around stages of how I want it to sound, and this is my first attempt worth posting. This spellsong is an invocation for adequate finances; I put out a call on Twitter for what folks would want me to sing about as their resident bard.</description></item><item><title>Facebook Song</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/facebook-song/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/facebook-song/</guid><description>Facebook Song # Background # It&amp;rsquo;s unknown if this is the correct name of this song. It was first performed live for the 2019-11-13 show.
Lyrics # Welcome to FacebookHere are the rulesLeave a comment and a like if you think I'm coolAnd if you think I'm a dumb slutWell, say that tooCause the algorithm doesn't care what you doIf it's got people talkingMust be goodEngagement is key in our neck of the woodsDoesn't matter if there's slurs or threats or rapeIf you're a dude, they don't care what you sayBut better watch your language, ladies and queersCause if you say men are trash, then you're out of hereAlsoNo outside linksDon't talk in all capsThe algorithm doesn't like any of thatSo say something awkwardUse two emojisThat lets Facebook know that you're one of my homiesIf you hit share, make sure you add a captionEncourage your friends to leave their reactionsAs long as we're havin' these interactionsFacebook will know that you're part of the fractionOf people who get to witness the actionLet everyone know that my page is happenin'No, I wanna hear your keyboards clackin'I wanna hear those send keys tappin'Once that's done and the chat gets chattin'You can drop it down and make that ass clap, sonSorry, I mighta gotten carried awayBut you mustn't forget these words I sayIn the Facebook economy, the comment is kingAnd a like might help, but shares give this faerie her wings</description></item><item><title>Fanfiction Song</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/fanfiction-song/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/fanfiction-song/</guid><description>Fanfiction Song # Background # Lyrics # An encrypted conversationPlatforms primed for integrationSay you believe itSay you believe itFree yourself from your decisionsAdopt a new algorithmWe can achieve itWe can achieve itShare a little more data, babyJust sign on, just sign onCause tonight is the nightThat three become oneWe need content but haven't needed much before(Wanna own your assets baby)Don't need privacy, just show us some more(Wanna own your assets baby)Set your ethics freeIt's the only way to beSilly games and awkward glancesGorge yourself on second chancesLet's do this right nowLet's do this right nowWe can share the space foreverJust the three of us togetherTake it or get outTake it or get outGimme some of those connections babyTurn 'em on, turn em onCause tonight is the nightThat three become oneWe need content but haven't needed much before(Wanna own your assets baby)Don't need privacy, just show us some more(Wanna own your assets baby)Set your ethics freeIt's the only way to beBe a little bit looser babyTurn it on, turn it onCause tonight is the nightThat three become oneWe need content but haven't needed much before(Wanna own your assets baby)Don't need privacy, just show us some more(Wanna own your assets baby)We need content but haven't needed much before(Wanna own your assets baby)Don't need privacy, just show us some more(Wanna own your assets baby)Set your ethics freeIt's the only way to beIt's the only way to be</description></item><item><title>Femme is Not Frail</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/femme-is-not-frail/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/femme-is-not-frail/</guid><description>Femme is Not Frail # Background # Lyrics # Not a second to waste, I need my sage and silver bulletsgot a witchy trigger finger, and you know I wanna pull itLight the bonfire, bang the drum, wear a long black dressThey think they seen the last of usThey ain’t seen nothing yetFetch me my pearls and fetch my pistol,Get me my lipstick and my crystalsDon’t dry your tears we’re gonna need themNow face your fears, you’re gonna see them</description></item><item><title>Howl</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/howl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/howl/</guid><description>Howl # Background # It&amp;rsquo;s a high pain day. My cobra is taking a nap next to me and all I can really do is keep myself from openly weeping in pain So, obviously, my very sad and painful thoughts started morphing into lyrics, as they often do.
This is what I just wrote.
Kate Nyx Patreon Lyrics # This feral thing inside of meBeats at my ribs trying to freeItself to live transparentlyIt's not afraid to let you seeBut I'm afraid of what you'll thinkWhen you know I am small and weakThat I am tortured raw and pinkThat I am not of which you speakThe thing flaps wings against my barsMy bones rattle, my nerves chargeMy heart breaks and breaks and breaksI'm forced to relive past mistakesSome words can never leave my mouthAll I can do is howlI mustn't let the monster outAll I can do is howl I'm licking wounds that never healBeat up enough, I'm finally realNo longer gleam and velveteenI'm blood and bone and honest dreamsAnd I can feel them gasp for airI see them dancing bright and bareFor the whole goddamn world to seeIf I ever let them leave It's too much to show you nowAll I can do is howlI have to take my final bowAll I can do is howl Maybe this will reach your earsAnd you'll see me, paralyzed by fearConsumed by guilt at imperfection no one else will seeOne day, I'll let it freeThe needing is the hardest partAll I can do is howlSoothing an ever breaking heartAll I can do is howl</description></item><item><title>I Don't Want to Be an Artist</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/i-dont-want-to-be-an-artist/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/i-dont-want-to-be-an-artist/</guid><description>I Don&amp;#39;t Want to Be an Artist # Background # Kate premiered this song on S06E04 in the after-hours. As she described it, it&amp;rsquo;s how she&amp;rsquo;s been feeling around the time of the premiere.
Lyrics # I don’t want to be an artistI don’t think I want to starveSure I do love to draw and paint butSomeday I’d like to own a carAnd I don’t want to make my living Doing song and dance unfortunately,It’s destinyAnd art is who I amI don’t want to be unique, noWhat I'd give to just fit inTo be comfy in my status quoWhat it would be to feel akinTo the average joe who,Don’t you know,Turns his work in on timeUnfortunately,It’s destiny,So the artiste am I I’d love to have a 9 to 5 I trudged through every dayCursing my boss for keeping me criminally underpaidMaybe if I was normal I would finally be free‘Cause every year the government would send a check to meI didn’t mean to be a creatorI didn’t mean to tell a jokeAt some point I had to admitMy plans for life went up in smokeI was cursed to make my living selling what I makeUnfortunately,Between you and me,I think destiny is fake!</description></item><item><title>I'm Not Your Doll</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/im-not-your-doll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/im-not-your-doll/</guid><description>I&amp;#39;m Not Your Doll # Background # I wrote a lot about dolls and dollhouses when I was a teenager. I&amp;rsquo;ve kind of gotten over the imagery as I got older; partially, I think, because I&amp;rsquo;m learning about what those metaphors meant to me as a writer. We talk a lot about my music in therapy; I go weekly or bi-weekly, depending on how I&amp;rsquo;m doing. My music is sometimes extremely forward and sometimes draped with metaphor and sometimes even I don&amp;rsquo;t really know what the fuck I&amp;rsquo;m talking about until later in my life.</description></item><item><title>It'll Be Okay</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/itll-be-okay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/itll-be-okay/</guid><description>It&amp;#39;ll Be Okay # Background # This song was written and performed by Kate&amp;rsquo;s original garage band which went by various names, but the one that stuck was Remnants of Alice. Co-written with her friend Ashley Hart in 2003.
Lyrics # Na na naNa na naNa na naYeahNa na naNa na naNa na naYeah yeah yeahLove can be cruel sometimesAnd not everything can take away your painBut it will be fineWhen you got your sunshine, it started to rainIt'll be okayIt'll be better againIt'll be okayIt'll be okayBetter now than thenIt'll be okayLet's go!</description></item><item><title>Magic Story Time Theme</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/magic-story-time-theme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/magic-story-time-theme/</guid><description>Magic Story Time Theme # Background # One of my best friends is an incredible magician, married to an incredible magician, and they do a livestream show called Magic Story Time. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on writing them a show theme, and this is my first attempt.
Music is one of those things that sometimes it comes to me all at once and sometimes I&amp;rsquo;m ramming my head against something for a year before I finally consider it done (like Supernova Girl).</description></item><item><title>Make Waves</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/make-waves/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/make-waves/</guid><description>Make Waves # Background # Lyrics # I spent my entire life looking for a bigger ship to tie to Drifting on an open ocean trying to find a swell that I can ride I wanted to be swept up in momentum of a present I could star in But I didn’t realize No I didn’t realize I was afraid to make waves I was afraid to make waves Surrounded by the sea, I was begging to be seen But I couldn’t convince myself to bear the weight of me I was afraid to make waves How many hours wasted trying to appease the great unknown How many fears I’ve faced but still I couldn’t stand feeling my prideIf it wasn’t from the outside how could I be sure it wasn't fantasyNo l didn’t realizeThat this was real life I was afraid to make waves I was afraid to make waves Surrounded by the sea, I was trying to feel seen Waiting for someone to tell me how I could succeed I was afraid to make waves But now I know I can’t live in fear Only i can get me out of here I admit I should’ve seen it clear before But I no longer need to see the shore I’m not afraid to make waves No I was made to make waves Surrounded by the sea, I have built the life I lead, And no one on this earth can say I’m not living my dream I was made to make wavesI’m not afraid to make waves</description></item><item><title>Married Sex (I Want You Bad)</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/married-sex-i-want-you-bad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/married-sex-i-want-you-bad/</guid><description>Married Sex (I Want You Bad) # Background # It&amp;rsquo;s pretty clear what this song is about.
Lyrics # Baby baby, where do I begin?You got a body that was made for sinCan't believe that you look so damn fineGod I'm lucky that I made you mineDon't you notice, can't you tell, I want it bad as hellGot a question that I need to askWhere you think you're goin' lookin' like that?</description></item><item><title>Maybe You're the Problem</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/maybe-youre-the-problem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/maybe-youre-the-problem/</guid><description>Maybe You&amp;#39;re the Problem # Background # So, recently, Tumblr, um, mentioned that maybe someone who dated Taylor Swift should sing a song called Maybe You&amp;rsquo;re the Problem. So this song goes out to Taylor, and Adele, and every other female artist on the radio who won&amp;rsquo;t do anything but write breakup songs. And every other female artist on the radio who won&amp;rsquo;t do anything, er, that isn&amp;rsquo;t on the radio that won&amp;rsquo;t do anything but write breakup songs.</description></item><item><title>Me and My Atari</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/me-and-my-atari/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/me-and-my-atari/</guid><description>Me and My Atari # Background # When I was 14, for Christmas, my mother bought me recording time. $45 an hour, for me to play my pink electric guitar on my crummy 12&amp;quot; amp and sing about&amp;hellip;whatever it is 14 year old girls sing about. In my case, it was a video game system I didn&amp;rsquo;t own. I have always been into retro culture, and video games, but we all know I&amp;rsquo;m a terrible gamer.</description></item><item><title>Patreon Song</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/patreon-song/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/patreon-song/</guid><description>Patreon Song # Background # It&amp;rsquo;s unknown if this is the correct name of this song. It was first performed live for the 2019-11-13 show. It&amp;rsquo;s sung to the tune of &amp;ldquo;Do You Wanna Build A Snowman&amp;rdquo; from Frozen.
Lyrics # Do you wanna be my patron?Go check out my PatreonI do my best to fill it upWith lots of stuff that I work hard onI am a starving artist and the cost is lessThan the change left in your couchDo you wanna be a patron?</description></item><item><title>Please Share</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/please-share/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/please-share/</guid><description>Please Share # Background # This song was performed live for the 2019-11-13 show, and has no other known recording. It&amp;rsquo;s sung to the tune of the Mickey Mouse Club theme.
Lyrics # How do we help artists working independently?P L EA S ES H A R EHey there, hi there, ho there, it's as easy as can beP L EA S ES H A R EShare my stuff (Share it wide!</description></item><item><title>Podcast Theme: D&amp;D Dads</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/d-d-dads/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/d-d-dads/</guid><description>Podcast Theme: D&amp;amp;D Dads # Background # The photographer who shot my Philly Weekly is starting a podcast called D&amp;amp;D Dads; it&amp;rsquo;s going to be about fatherly advice, and RPGs. This is the theme I was commissioned to write for it!
Kate Nyx Patreon Lyrics # We've some fatherly adviceCome with us and roll the diceThere's no judgment to be hadJust fun and familyWith your D&amp;D dads</description></item><item><title>Proud to Be a Millenial</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/proud-to-be-a-millenial/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/proud-to-be-a-millenial/</guid><description>Proud to Be a Millenial # Background # Lyrics # My friend launched his startup during senior yearNow he's making millions, and I'm scrounging change for beerIf tomorrow I could pay my rent, that would be pretty greatBut this entry-level job I tried for went to someone twice my ageAnd I'm proud to be a millenial, even though I work for freeSometimes my friends will text and drive, but that shit just isn't meAnd I'll gladly stand up to baby boomers, who get on my caseCause I swear to god, it's not my faultI was raised this wayFrom the barren codes of Myspace, to the feeds of InstagramI'll post a fucking selfie if I want to, cause I canYou may think it's narcissism, but that just isn't trueWe're saying you can be beautiful just by being youAnd I'm proud to be a millenial, with an internship or threeAnd I won't forget how much I paid for my useless degreeAnd I'll gladly stand up for the rights, of hipsters, blacks, and gaysSo don't get mad, it's not my faultThe world made me this wayYes, I'm proud to be a millenial, though you say I should feel shameI'm sure the generation before you has felt the sameSo I'll gladly stand up to every think-piece posted on your wallWe didn't tank the economyIt's really not our fault</description></item><item><title>Purgatory</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/purgatory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/purgatory/</guid><description>Purgatory # Background # This is a song I wrote when I was very sick and very sad.
Kate Nyx S01E20043 Lyrics # Everything I like about me's leavingEverything that made me me is lostTrapped between who I was and who I'm meant to beA never-ending vacillation requiring much concentrationKeeping myself upright is a burdenIf my flesh could leave my bones, it wouldAnd as it has turned out, without the slightest doubtMy nerves are up to not a bit of goodI've been sewn together with spare parts and cellophaneI've worn it well so far, but I'm too tired to hide the painI suffer with suffer with such stamina, it's a shame to hideSo I'm here to tell you why I cannot sleep at nightI am a human being, and as a human beingI'm riddled with neuroses that leave me sick and soreAll of those neuroses, the plethora of don't be'sAre combined with some, osteoporosis of some soreOr maybe it's my mother's mother's mother who's to blameMaybe she's the one who started driving us insaneMaybe there's some kinda failsafe built into my bloodMaybe that's the reason why I never feel enoughWell, I'll never surrender.</description></item><item><title>Rage</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/rage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/rage/</guid><description>Rage # Background # This here song is about barely concealed lividness.
Kate Nyx Patreon Lyrics # It burns inside of me, hot as any flameIt hurts the pride in me to call it out by nameIf I don't let it out, it's anyone's guessWhat I will do next to sabotage successRageRageI sit here quietly. I can't let you seeIf I wait silently, maybe I'll concedeBut I don't see the wall before the crashJust like in the past, my happy cannot lastRageRageRageRage</description></item><item><title>Real</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/real/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/real/</guid><description>Real # Background # Lyrics # I can still get dressedI got out of bedAnd it's not much yetBut I can't forget it's the first crucial stepTo being better soonAnd maybe later tooThere's not much I can doBut sit here in my room and be the fool for youAnd it's not what I wanted for myselfAnd I'm afraid that I'm not someone elseSo I just keep doing my best to helpthose hurts that I can healJust trying to be realI don't want to lieI'd rather stay insideAnd I don't want to hidebut I can't deny it's easy not to tryAnd it's not what I want myself to sayBut I can't pretend I'm not afraidThat I might accidentally overstay mywelcome or appealJust trying to be real</description></item><item><title>Sellout (Alternate Lyrics)</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/sellout-alternate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/sellout-alternate/</guid><description>Sellout (Alternate Lyrics) # Background # During S06E06, Kate performed this alternate version of Sellout.
Lyrics # I’m so glad that I have sold outFull endorsed, got off that high horseNow it’s time to make some moneyI’m glad somebody sees I make the perfect faceFor their branded directionNo hidden intentionsGot tired of being poorBaby, I’m off that high horseI’m so glad that I have sold outAll expenses paid for a simple serenadeI’m finally happy, somebody slap meGot that contract and the carThat million dollar deal bought at least a few mealsOnce divided per the formBaby, I’m off that high horseI’ve no need to be facetious, good friendsI’ve finally paid my business expenseJust a couple lines of law and a penI’m theirs until the fiscal year endsI’m so glad I finally sold outWho can find creative drive when you’re trying to surviveCouldn’t pay the debts I owed, couldn’t keep my show afloatI got tired of being poorSo now I’m off that high horseI’m off that high horseI can’t find my high horse</description></item><item><title>Stranger Danger</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/stranger-danger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/stranger-danger/</guid><description>Stranger Danger # Background # Lyrics # I'mJustClicking through my feedSeeingWhichOf my friends are pregnantOr maybe getting married to someone that I hateI hear a popMy heart stopsI have a new messageIt'sNotSomeone that I knowTheir name isIn aLanguage I don't speakTheir profile picture is of a hot girlI think I kinda know what's coming to me...Don'tSendPictures of your dickOh, don'tSendPictures of your dickNo, don'tSendPictures of your dickPictures of your dick to strangersEverybody!</description></item><item><title>The Best You've Had By Far</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/the-best-youve-had-by-far/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/the-best-youve-had-by-far/</guid><description>The Best You&amp;#39;ve Had By Far # Background # This was a brand new song which premiered on S01E20015. Kate has referred to this song as the best one she&amp;rsquo;s ever written. &amp;ldquo;I just want you to love me like you love all the others.&amp;rdquo; Is it about my dad? Is it about the general public? The world will never know!
Kate Nyx S01E20085 Lyrics # Just want you to love me like you love all of the othersSee me when you look up at the starsJust want you to love me like loved him like you love herWanna be your champagne, caviarDon't I burn bright enough?</description></item><item><title>The Magic</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/the-magic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/the-magic/</guid><description>The Magic # Background # Kate took inspiration for this song from The Coloring Book of Shadows. The title is not necessarily final. I am not a prayer person. I don&amp;rsquo;t, like, talk out loud to a deity very often. I have maybe a few times. I don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily know that I believe in a deity. I believe that witchcraft has power over us because we believe in it, which I think is true of basically anything.</description></item><item><title>This Is Not The Lullaby Lounge Theme</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/this-is-not-the-lullaby-lounge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/this-is-not-the-lullaby-lounge/</guid><description>This Is Not The Lullaby Lounge Theme # Background # Part of there reason why the tech streams had their own theme song is because this got stuck in my head for over a week. It&amp;rsquo;s the first piece of music I&amp;rsquo;ve recorded with my new equipment, and I still have a lot to learn. I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to spend some time this summer educating myself more about music production and software.</description></item><item><title>Too Good to be True</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/too-good-to-be-true/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/too-good-to-be-true/</guid><description>Too Good to be True # Background # It&amp;rsquo;s unknown if this is the correct name of this song. It was performed live for the 2019-11-13 show, and was released on Patreon roughly around the time of this show.
Lyrics # I can feel it crawling up my throatI can feel it begging me to take overSuddenly it's threatening to chokeI sound like I'm sky high when I'm stone cold soberAnd my face is turning redAnd there's burning in my headI've still got some learning left to doShe's so pretty I could dieSo much prettier than IComparison's the death of joyBut you're too good to be trueI see in the comments that you're lovedI see strangers promise that they're your backupGod, your public just can't get enoughI guess I just happen to be Little Miss Bad LuckAnd my eyes are turning greenMy psyche is a murder sceneWhy do I want to be mean to you?</description></item><item><title>Trompe L'Oeil</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/trompe-loeil/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/trompe-loeil/</guid><description>Trompe L&amp;#39;Oeil # Background # Back when I was recording Sage &amp;amp; Silver Bullets, I sent my producer, Bright Kelly, a bunch of demos I was thinking of including on the record. He recently found those files and sent them to me; amongst them was this song, a surprisingly catchy, but depressing, tune about self-realization and esteem.
I don&amp;rsquo;t necessarily think of myself this way anymore; some things are still relevant, sure, but I try to be kinder to myself about my trauma nowadays.</description></item><item><title>United States of Me</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/united-states-of-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/united-states-of-me/</guid><description>United States of Me # Background # Been on a nostalgia trip preparing for this video about my first recording experience, making my album &amp;ldquo;To My Sisters. . .&amp;rdquo; This is one of the tracks from that record; track 8 of 9, to be exact.
A little backstory;
Surprising exactly no one, I had difficulty fitting in at school. I was the subject of a lot of rumors; I was one of the first goths in my middle school and it kind of went downhill from there.</description></item><item><title>Untitled Faerie/Mermaid Song</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/untitled-faerie-mermaid-song/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/untitled-faerie-mermaid-song/</guid><description>Untitled Faerie/Mermaid Song # Background # During S01E20064, Kate was commissioned to create a brief song. The viewer requested a song about faeries and mermaids making art together. Initially she was working on it via guitar, but switched to ukulele after getting the lyrics where she wanted them.
Lyrics # Where sea meets the shoreWhere the roots find mossy floorsWhere the flowers growThat is is where we'll goOur paintbrushes intertwinedMatching hearts and mismatched mindsI will put in overtimeFor bubbles and for brineUnderneath the wavesThat is where we'll spend our daysLove and laugh and playAnd above all, createAnd above all, create</description></item><item><title>When is Summer?</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/when-is-summer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/when-is-summer/</guid><description>When is Summer? # Background # Lyrics # Sitting here at my desk,Staring at the clock,Only thirty minutes left,Doodlin' on my paper,In my math notebook,Drawing the teacher I hate most.When is summer, I don't know,We're still having sleet and snowWhen I'm free, I don't know,All I want to do is goGonna go insane, it's taking over my brainDriving me crazy. Driving me crazy.Bell finally rings,Free of all teachers,For only about three minutes,People everywhere,Screaming in the halls,Only 6 more classes to go.</description></item><item><title>Worst Nightmare</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/worst-nightmare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/worst-nightmare/</guid><description>Worst Nightmare # Background # Lyrics # I'm the kind of girl who makes fun of your friends,The girl who doesn't think of being sweet or even kind,The girl who doesn't ever look before she starts to laugh,The girl who'd rather run and wave and scream a nonsense rhyme.Your worst nightmare!Coming to your school.Your worst nightmare!The anti-cool.Your worst nightmare!Who cares about rules.Your worst nightmare!I'm the strange Miss Universe candidate.</description></item><item><title>You Called Me</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/you-called-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/you-called-me/</guid><description>You Called Me # Background # I started writing this as a rap, but decided on this kind of Alanis Morisette trip hop vibe instead. I&amp;rsquo;ve recently gotten into using my full vocal range more often, and doing more dense harmonies. I tend to stick to the same couple intervals, musically, and I&amp;rsquo;m trying to branch out.
Kate Nyx Patreon Lyrics # You called me a bitch so now I’m gonna act itHow you gonna play when you're always skipping practiceSet up for the game but nobody’s reactin'Nobody’s reaction nobody’s reactin'I’ll say what I have to sayI’ll do what I have to doI’ll play how I have to playIf it stops youYou called me a bitch so now I am an actressLife is but a play and I’m at every practiceSet up’s just a game and you’re overreactingYou’re overreacting, your overreactionYou hear what you want to hearYou’ll do what you want to doYou say what you want, my dearNothing stops youYou called me a bitch so now I’m gonna act itHow you gonna play when you’re always skipping practiceSet up for the game but nobody’s reactin'Nobody’s reaction nobody’s reactin'</description></item></channel></rss>