<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Unreleased Songs on Nyxipedia</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/</link><description>Recent content in Unreleased Songs on Nyxipedia</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Be My Valentine</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/be-my-valentine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/be-my-valentine/</guid><description>Be My Valentine # Background # This is a song Kate wrote at about 14 years old, and memorable and important because she played it for her first gig at a bar at 16 years old.
Lyrics # Got you candyI bought you flowersStood outside your windowFor three hoursHolding up a stereo like the guy in the movie didWrote you poemsEight love lettersYou don't like meAny betterDo you think I'm serious, or do you think I'm just a kid?</description></item><item><title>Don't Send Pictures of your Dick</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/dont-send-pictures-of-your-dick/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/dont-send-pictures-of-your-dick/</guid><description>Don&amp;#39;t Send Pictures of your Dick # Background # It&amp;rsquo;s unknown if this is the correct name of this song. It was performed live for the 2019-11-06 show, and has no other known recording.
Lyrics # I'mJustClicking through my feedSeeingWhichOf my friends are pregnantOr maybe getting married to someone that I hateI hear a popMy heart stopsI have a new messageIt'sNotSomeone that I knowTheir name isIn aLanguage I don't speakTheir profile picture is of a hot girlI think I kinda know what's coming to me.</description></item><item><title>Facebook Song</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/facebook-song/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/facebook-song/</guid><description>Facebook Song # Background # It&amp;rsquo;s unknown if this is the correct name of this song. It was first performed live for the 2019-11-13 show.
Lyrics # Welcome to FacebookHere are the rulesLeave a comment and a like if you think I'm coolAnd if you think I'm a dumb slutWell, say that tooCause the algorithm doesn't care what you doIf it's got people talkingMust be goodEngagement is key in our neck of the woodsDoesn't matter if there's slurs or threats or rapeIf you're a dude, they don't care what you sayBut better watch your language, ladies and queersCause if you say men are trash, then you're out of hereAlsoNo outside linksDon't talk in all capsThe algorithm doesn't like any of thatSo say something awkwardUse two emojisThat lets Facebook know that you're one of my homiesIf you hit share, make sure you add a captionEncourage your friends to leave their reactionsAs long as we're havin' these interactionsFacebook will know that you're part of the fractionOf people who get to witness the actionLet everyone know that my page is happenin'No, I wanna hear your keyboards clackin'I wanna hear those send keys tappin'Once that's done and the chat gets chattin'You can drop it down and make that ass clap, sonSorry, I mighta gotten carried awayBut you mustn't forget these words I sayIn the Facebook economy, the comment is kingAnd a like might help, but shares give this faerie her wings</description></item><item><title>It'll Be Okay</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/itll-be-okay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/itll-be-okay/</guid><description>It&amp;#39;ll Be Okay # Background # This song was written and performed by Kate&amp;rsquo;s original garage band which went by various names, but the one that stuck was Remnants of Alice. Co-written with her friend Ashley Hart in 2003.
Lyrics # Na na naNa na naNa na naYeahNa na naNa na naNa na naYeah yeah yeahLove can be cruel sometimesAnd not everything can take away your painBut it will be fineWhen you got your sunshine, it started to rainIt'll be okayIt'll be better againIt'll be okayIt'll be okayBetter now than thenIt'll be okayLet's go!</description></item><item><title>Patreon Song</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/patreon-song/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/patreon-song/</guid><description>Patreon Song # Background # It&amp;rsquo;s unknown if this is the correct name of this song. It was first performed live for the 2019-11-13 show. It&amp;rsquo;s sung to the tune of &amp;ldquo;Do You Wanna Build A Snowman&amp;rdquo; from Frozen.
Lyrics # Do you wanna be my patron?Go check out my PatreonI do my best to fill it upWith lots of stuff that I work hard onI am a starving artist and the cost is lessThan the change left in your couchDo you wanna be a patron?</description></item><item><title>Please Share</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/please-share/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/please-share/</guid><description>Please Share # Background # This song was performed live for the 2019-11-13 show, and has no other known recording. It&amp;rsquo;s sung to the tune of the Mickey Mouse Club theme.
Lyrics # How do we help artists working independently?P L EA S ES H A R EHey there, hi there, ho there, it's as easy as can beP L EA S ES H A R EShare my stuff (Share it wide!</description></item><item><title>The Best You've Had By Far</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/the-best-youve-had-by-far/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/the-best-youve-had-by-far/</guid><description>The Best You&amp;#39;ve Had By Far # Background # This was a brand new song which premiered on S01E20015. Kate has referred to this song as the best one she&amp;rsquo;s ever written.
Lyrics # Just want you to love me like you love all of the othersSee me when you look up at the starsJust want you to love me like loved him like you love herWanna be your champagne, caviarDon't I burn bright enough?</description></item><item><title>Too Good to be True</title><link>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/too-good-to-be-true/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nyxipedia.com/music/unreleased-songs/too-good-to-be-true/</guid><description>Too Good to be True # Background # It&amp;rsquo;s unknown if this is the correct name of this song. It was performed live for the 2019-11-13 show, and was released on Patreon roughly around the time of this show.
Lyrics # I can feel it crawling up my throatI can feel it begging me to take overSuddenly it's threatening to chokeI sound like I'm sky high when I'm stone cold soberAnd my face is turning redAnd there's burning in my headI've still got some learning left to doShe's so pretty I could dieSo much prettier than IComparison's the death of joyBut you're too good to be trueI see in the comments that you're lovedI see strangers promise that they're your backupGod, your public just can't get enoughI guess I just happen to be Little Miss Bad LuckAnd my eyes are turning greenMy psyche is a murder sceneWhy do I want to be mean to you?</description></item></channel></rss>